

TAKATA KEI

Full stack & Blockchain Engineer

goldone0101@gmail.com

💡 5-chōme-46-4 Yoyogi Shibuya City, Tokyo 151-0053, Japan linkedin.com/in/takata-kei-023292242

github.com/goldoneen

t.me/goldoneen

live:.cid.abecc0e8069e6d36

goldoneen.github.io

CAREER SUMMARY

Experienced full stack developer with a strong background in developing awardwinning applications for a diverse clientele. 7+ years of industry experience includes programming, debugging, and wireframes. Also, I handle tasks with accuracy and efficiency. I love to write code in a high-paced and challenging environment with an emphasis on using best practices to develop high quality software that meets project requirements, budget, and schedule. As a developer, enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleagues.

WORK EXPERIENCE SKILLS

Blockchain full stack Engineer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

 Built sophisticated smart contracts like staking marketplace offers, troubleshot production issues, contributed to gas fee optimization, and deployed into Ethereum mainnet.

 Migrated smart contracts from Ethereum to Polygon and existing assets (NFTs, offers, collections) to newly deployed contracts on Polygon.

Performed a Web3 integration with the smart contracts on Next.js.

• Built subgraph endpoints to interact with the smart contract triggered events and deploy them into the graph protocol.

Worked closely with other protocols like Rarible, Aave, and Compound.

Technologies:

Solidity Ethereum Polygon Web3.js Subgraph

DigitalaxFull stack HTML/CSS/SCSS

JavaScript/Typescript

React/Vue/Angular

Next/Nuxt/Gatsby

WordPress/Shopify

Node.js/ASP.NET Python/Ruby/PHP

AWS/GCP/Azure

PostgreSQL/MySQL/MongoDB

Blockchain Full-stack Engineer

Feb 2021 - Oct 2021

Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js.

Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.

Created a POC Vue.js front-end platform for an NFT gallery using Moralis and Vue 3.

 Worked on the token distribution and migration from BSC to Polygon network using BscScan, PolygonScan API, and Solidity.

Technologies:

Blockchain Web3.js Solidity Ethers.js Moralis React Vue.js JavaScript

Looksrare

Blockchain

Web3.js/Ether.js

Solidity/Rust

Hardhat/Truffle

Infura/Moralis

Eth/BSC/Polygon/Avalanche/Solana

Blockchain Full-stack Engineer

May 2020 - Jan 2021

Developed automated trading strategies on Uniswap and QuickSwap.

Built smart contract with solidity and deployed using Truffle.

Used Flashbots API to fetch block info regarding trading pool and staking.

 Worked on building trading view, swap modal using React, Next, TypeScript, Webs.js, and Subgraph.

Supported limit orders on the Ethereum Mainnet and Polygon (Matic).

PROFESSIONAL Gelato Network

> Effective communication Team player

Strong problem solver

Good time management

Fast learner

Technologies:

Web3.js Solidity Blockchain Ethers.js React Ethereum JavaScript Ploygon

EDUCATION

MSc in Computer Science

2011 - 2015

Cave Consulting GroupThe University of Tokyo

Angular Developer

Jan 2019 - Mar 2020

 Developed an Angular, RxJS, and Angular Material web app for managing user registration for seminars and webinars hosting in Firebase.

 Created a Node.js back end with Firebase cloud function and Firestore as the database LANGUAGE while Google Storage was used as file storage.

Took 100% responsibility for the project of planning, architecture, development, and deployment.

English (Fluent)

Technologies:

Angular Firebase Node.js JavaScript Material-UI Bootstrap Google API

INTERESTS

Front end Developer

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018

Holidu Climbing

Swimming Integrated Redux and MobX on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better

Travelling

state management of React components. Implemented a GraphQL-and-Apollo server for a React-and-Vue.js front-end data query. Photography

Created a new customized chart library using D3.js and Plotly.js.

 Embedded a Google tag manager and Google Analytics for the website conversion tracking and the user event tracking.

Technologies:

GraphQL React TypeScript Material UI

Full-stack Web Developer

Techno Pro

May 2015 - Dec 2017

- Worked as intern developer on Web and mobile application developments.
- Built out several websites with PHP, Node.js and Javascript frameworks.

Technologies:

jQuery JavaScript WordPress Node.js React Vue.js PHP